Sun Wukong was born on the Mount Hua Guo, the sacred island of Dongsheng.
He learned 72 different kinds of magic.
Then he became the Great Sage of Heaven.
Due to the chaos in the sky,
he was made by Buddha Shakyamuni
and was taken to Mount Wujing.
In the 13th year of Zhen Guan,
Tang Sanzang took the scriptures from the West.
He removed Sun Wukong's 500-year curse,
and purified Sun Wukong.
Tang Sanzang went to Mount Hua Guo
to take the scriptures from the West.
He went to Mount Hua Guo to take the scriptures from the West.
On the journey of seven days, Sun Wukong protected Tang Sanzang
and saved Jinjiao and Yingjiao
and defeated Princess Iron Fan, the Demon King.
Finally, he took over the Bajiao Mountain
and safely crossed the Fiery Mountain.
The Four Seasons
After 14 years of the journey,
In the year 640 A.D.
Tang Sanzang has traveled through 14 states
and traveled more than 11,000 miles.
The four disciples are not afraid of danger
and continue to travel to more than 90 countries in the west.
Hurry up!
Harder!
Wukong, what kind of rule is this
when a monk is under supervision?
I don't know, but I've never seen it before.
Hurry up!
Master, are you the master of Sanzang?
Yes, I am.
This is not a place to talk.
Master, I'll meet you at Zhiyun Temple in the east of the city tonight.
Greetings, Master.
Please rise.
I am Zhiguang, the host of Zhiyun Temple.
Although I don't know you,
I've seen you in my dream.
You've seen me in your dream?
It was a Bodhisattva who often asked me to dream.
He said that you have three disciples
who can help us rebuild Buddhism.
Zhiguang, although Buddhism is different,
why do you worship Buddhism
and not the monks?
In Chechi, there were two sects of Buddhism
who were under the control of King Chechi.
However, three years ago,
there was a drought in the whole country.
Two Taoists from foreign countries came
and called for help.
They openly challenged the monks
and begged for help.
However, the Taoists won.
King Chechi worshiped the Taoists
and listened to their advice.
They destroyed the Buddha statue
and forced the monks to build the Taoist temple.
What are the names of the two Taoists?
Lu Li Da Xian and Yang Li Da Xian.
What a strange name!
They don't look like human beings.
They look like animals.
They might be monsters.
Master, Bajie Wu Jing and I
are going to inquire about these two Taoists.
Someone is coming.
There's no one inside.
I don't know what to do.
Right.
Someone is coming.
What should we do?
Let's go.
One, two, one, two, three, four.
Three-leaf dragon-hose horse.
The sky is clear.
The earth is clear.
Please come in.
Please follow me.
I will be your guide.
Why did you hit me?
I didn't hit you.
You hit me first.
Did the Buddha hit me?
Not bad.
I hit you.
The Buddha is coming.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Lu Li and Yang Li.
We are here in the Heaven.
But you stayed up all night.
We are very touched.
So we are here to give you a blessing.
Right.
Your Majesty, thank you very much.
I am very grateful.
I have nothing to ask for.
I just want to live forever.
Please bless me, Your Majesty.
What a coincidence.
We brought you holy water.
Holy water?
As long as you drink our holy water,
you will live forever.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
But the holy water comes from the Immortal Realm.
If you don't drink our holy water,
you can't peek.
I dare not peek.
Attention, everyone.
Turn around.
We are going to drink our holy water now.
Where did you get the holy water?
I got it from the toilet.
Great. I have been preparing for a long time.
Did you hear the sound of the holy water?
Yes, I did.
Lu Li, Yang Li.
The holy water is not good enough.
Drink it.
Drink less.
It tastes strange.
It's sour and salty.
It tastes like pig urine.
It tastes like monkey urine.
You are right.
It's not holy water.
It's holy urine.
You just drank Song Wukong's urine.
Good boy.
He drank Song Wukong's urine.
It doesn't matter.
Since he dares to fool us,
I will kill him.
I will kill him before and after.
Lu Li and Yang Li are really devils.
Master,
according to my judgment,
they are definitely devils.
Master,
tomorrow morning,
we will meet King Che Chi.
We will invite King Che Chi to pray to the Buddha
to enlighten the disciples of Buddha.
Amitabha.
Mr. Tang,
you want me to pray to the Buddha
to enlighten the monks?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Wait.
Mr. Tang is a good man.
He is arrogant and arrogant.
He is an arrogant monk.
That's why I don't agree to enlighten the monks.
How can you say that
the monk is arrogant and arrogant?
Seven years ago,
King Che Chi suffered a great drought.
It was because these stupid monks
didn't know how to pray,
but they deceived the King.
They thought they could pray to the Buddha.
If we hadn't arrived in time,
the millions of lives of King Che Chi
would have died long ago.
Master Jia is also a monk.
How do you know that he doesn't know how to pray?
Mr. Tang,
do you know how to pray?
I...
I don't know how to pray.
Master,
you know how to pray.
I know that you know how to pray.
If I know how to pray,
do you dare to compete with me?
If you dare to compete with me,
I will definitely accompany you.
Your Majesty,
since the beginning of this year,
there has been no rain.
The people have prayed for rain several times.
Since Tang San Zang praised the sea,
I am willing to compete with him.
Very good.
Tang San Zang,
you dare to compete with the State Preceptor?
If you win a battle,
I will be the first monk.
If there is no rain,
I will bring you back to the execution ground
and punish you.
If there is no wind,
I will alone let you go.
It's not too much,
I only'll cmk anything...
Those who have been given sun and heat,
You two protect the master, I'll go up and have a look
It's you
Who told you to shoot the thunder here
Master, the mortal world has passed the Wulai Order
We are following the order
I don't care where that demon comes from
Who will help that demon
It's just that I can't get through
Master, we don't dare
As long as you order, we will do as you say
Very well, I'll be in charge of everything
The wind is gone, the thunder is gone
It's okay, let's do it again
It's raining
Lu Li, what's wrong
Lu Li
Senior, it must be Senior
Your Majesty, your master's magic is no longer working
Do you want my master to come and ask for rain?
All right
Chief Tang, it's your turn to ask for rain
I...
Master, master, come and ask for rain
I don't know how to ask for rain
Master, Wukong, ask for rain
How do I ask for rain
Read the sutra
What sutra
Just read it
Read the sutra
Lu Li, wake up
Wake up
Let go
Yes
The wind is coming
It's really raining
Master Yang, you're really good
It's raining
It's not my wine, it's the monk's wine
Chief Tang, you really got a great achievement
Let's send an order to release the monk
You can't release the monk
Yes, I can't release him
You dare to disobey the order
Yes, not only do I have to disobey the order
I also have to disobey the order
Yes, I will
I'll beat you to death
Kill him
Senior, why don't you come back
Let's go
This monkey is really good
Let's stay
Your Majesty, I was wronged
I almost got beaten by them
Now I decide to follow Buddhism
Zhiguang, thank the King
Amitabha
Thank you, Your Majesty
Your Majesty
Yang Li, I think we shouldn't deal with those spiders
I think we should go
Okay, let's go
No
These two are Luli and Yang Li
Luli and Yang Li
As the State Preceptor of Chuchu
What brings you here today, State Preceptor?
Tang Sanzang broke our Five Thunder Law
He made us brothers lose our power in Chuchu
Tang Sanzang
Tang Sanzang is a monk from Qujing
If you eat his flesh, you can live a long life
As long as you avenge us
You can eat Tang Sanzang
Tang Sanzang's flesh can live a long life
Absolutely
Where is Tang Sanzang now?
He will be here in a couple of days
Okay
Sister, let's lure him into the cave
Your Majesty, the cave is scary
Tang Sanzang is a monk
And he has Sun Wukong to protect him
Will he be able to sing easily?
Bajie
You're here
Master
How many steamed buns do we have left?
Four
Great
Let's split them
Master, we can't split them
Why can't we split them?
There were four steamed buns
But now they are in my stomach
You're greedy
Go to the flower shop
Okay
Bajie
Don't go
I'll go
Master
You used to go to the flower shop
Today you have to perform
You have to go to the flower shop
Master
Please help me
I don't want you to go to the flower shop
I'll go
Wukong
The Buddha's teaching is hard work
You can't always do what you want
It's good for you to go to the flower shop
Yes
I'll go
Master
You have to be careful
I will
Be careful
Master
You have to be careful
It's all your fault
I'm Tang Sanzang
I want to go to the West Heaven
I'm not from here
I came to Mu Hua
You're Tang Sanzang?
Yes
Bajie
Tang Sanzang doesn't want to come
Are you really Tang Sanzang?
Yes
I'm just passing by
I want to draw a picture
Please go to the inner city
And draw a picture
Yes
Master
Please draw
Tang Sanzang
Master
These are the treasures I prepared for you
Is it not to your taste?
I'll take my leave
Master has been gone for two hours
Why hasn't he come back yet?
Did he have an accident?
Master is so stupid
Silly people are so stupid
He won't have an accident
I'm worried
Let's go find Master
Bajie
Are you taking a bath?
Who are you?
My name is Zhu Bajie
Bajie
A monk has just come
And another fat pig
It's so lively today
Monk, are you Tang Sanzang?
Do you know Tang Sanzang?
He's my master
Where is he?
Fat pig
Do you want to take a bath with us?
Take a bath?
I haven't taken a bath for three months
If you want to take a bath with me
I'll do it today
I'll take a bath with you
Look at my body
I'll show you how to dive
So hard
Help
Put me down
Senior
He hasn't come back for so long
Did he have an accident?
Help
Bajie
Senior
What's going on?
I...
Senior
I caught seven female demons
And then...
And then?
And then you were caught and hanged here
Why are you taking off your clothes?
No
I did it myself
What kind of monster is that?
You need to take off your clothes to catch them?
Senior
I'm begging you
Let me down
They took Master away
Where did they take Master?
I don't know
Maybe near here
Fat pig
How dare you go against us
I'm going to chop you into eight pieces
And make a big meal
Yes
Yang Li, Lu Lie
Do you really want to eat him?
Of course
We can live forever if we eat him
I've changed my mind
I don't want to eat him
Why?
What?
Tang Sanzang is handsome
And there are few men in the mountain
It's a pity
Bajie
Do you like him?
He's got spirit
I like him
Bajie
Since you like him
Then you should get back at him
And marry him
Marry him?
Then we're even
I agree
Over there
Zhuang Shan Si Pan
Idiot
Tan Si Shan Zhuang
Senior
They seem to be having a wedding
Come
Senior
The groom looks familiar
I think I've seen him somewhere
Yes, I think I've seen him somewhere
Of course
The groom is our master
Master
Master is a monk
How can he get married?
That's strange
That's good
Master can get married
I'll go out and have a good time
Bajie, don't make a fuss
It's impossible
Let's take a closer look
The two families get married
The husband and wife get married
The bride and groom get married
Who's afraid of who?
Send them to the bridal chamber
Wait
Monkey, are you getting married?
You've come at the right time
A monk's wedding is the best
Are you here to have a drink?
Shut up
Lu Li Yang
So it was you two
Master, let's go
He won't leave
He's decided to stay with me forever
I don't believe it
Master is not that kind of person
San Zhang
They don't believe you're going to marry me
Go and tell them
Wukong, I've decided to get married
Go back to Xiancheng and forget Xi Tian
I've been with you for so long
And now I realize you like to joke
Master, you really like to joke
I'm not joking
Master, are you really going to marry him?
He's a demon
They're not demons
They're all beauties
Master, you're leaving us
Where are you taking us?
There are many beauties here
If you're willing to stay
I'll be your matchmaker
You can get married
Master
Wukong, I think you should all stay
I'll help you get married
Yes, we'll get married every night
Get married every night
Fatty, do you want to stay?
Me?
Yes
Senior, they're demons
We're human after all
Fatty, you can stay
Really? Can I stay?
I think you'll be eaten by them in three days
Master has fallen into their trap
Trap?
What about Master?
If they want to get married, we'll fight
Let's go
Yes
Master
Senior
Junior, let's go
I think you should eat them
Go
Yes
Help
Senior
Master
Go away
Hurry
Help
Go away
Master
Where's my bride?
Master, your bride is over there
I don't want that monster
I want my bride
Bride
Master
I'm looking for my bride
She's going to marry me
Master
I'm looking for my bride
Look at me
Master, you fell into my trap
I'll untie your shoes for him
Take it
I'll untie it
Master
I don't want to see you dance
I'm looking for my bride
Master
Wukong, why am I dressed like this?
Master, you fell in love with a monster
You're going to marry him
Sister Ma, I'm a Buddhist
How can I talk nonsense?
What's going on?
Wujing, what's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
My face touched Master's hand
That monkey is really good
Yes
Let's go
Brother, I don't think we can make it
Yes
Stop
Who are you? What do you want?
We have no grudge
How dare you
How dare you break into the human bones
Take him
Master
Where did you get these two Taoists?
They broke into our human bones
They broke into the forbidden area
They must be spies
Master, we're not spies
We're the masters of the country
I don't care what kind of master you are
According to the rules of this valley
Whoever breaks into the forbidden area will have to live for three days
And have to die
Have to live for three days
That's right
You're better
You go first
Me first?
Master, I'm too fat
It's all fat
Fat is not delicious
I think it's better to roast it first
Makes sense
I'm too tired of eating fat
You go first
Master, I'm dry and thin
It's really not delicious
I have skin disease
Let's roast it first
No, it's still delicious
I'm too fat
You can't roast it
What should I do?
Master
I have an idea
What idea?
Tell me
Go
It turns out that these two masters
One is Yang, the other is Lu
Your Majesty
We don't want to use fire to roast them
Don't roast us
Thank you, Your Majesty
No
Your Majesty
I want to stew them
Stew them
Yes, stew them
It's better
Your Majesty
Your Majesty, don't eat us
But you must eat us
Let me introduce you
A fat, white, tender and delicious food
It's not just delicious
It's also long-lasting
Long-lasting?
Who are you talking about?
A monk from the East
His name is Tang San Zang
Your Majesty, I want to eat Tang San Zang's meat
Tell me, where is he?
Not far from here
But he has a disciple named Sun Wukong
That monkey, you can't deal with him
Sun Wukong
Is he the Sun Wukong who made a scene
Seven hundred years ago?
Yes
This monkey is really hard to deal with
Your Majesty, I have an idea
My darling, what idea do you have?
You
Get out of my way
I'll send him to deal with him first
No
Master
Why did you spend so much time in the garden?
If you want to spend more time
Why don't you go and paint yourself?
Miss
Be careful when you walk
Are you going to the West to collect gold?
Yes
He is my master, Tang San Zang
Then you must be Brother Ba Jie
Yes, how did you know?
I was waiting for you
Your Majesty
My family has been kind
I heard that you were passing by
I have prepared some money to pay you
Master
Move
Why did you kill me?
Miss
He is dead
Why did you kill him?
He is a demon
He is loyal
He is a kind village girl
He is not a demon
Wukong
I'll prove it to you
Brother, what are you doing?
Move
What's wrong?
He is a demon
No, he used magic to change the body
He is lying to you
Wukong, why did you do that?
Zhu Ba Jie, be careful
Master
It's true that you killed him
I didn't do it
Master
Wukong
Help
Master
Master, stop
Wukong
You can't change your nature
It's too easy to kill
I forgive you
But you can't kill yourself again
Otherwise, you will die
Master
Wukong really has a trick
He saw through me
Fortunately, I was able to see through him
Now, Tang Sanzang is against him
Good
Wukong
You can't be so clever
I'm so lucky to have you here.
Good, good, good.
Are you satisfied now?
Yes.
Where are you?
My daughter, where are you?
My daughter, come back!
Oh no, he's looking for someone.
My daughter, where are you?
My daughter, my daughter!
That was his daughter.
Another monster.
Come back!
Did you see my daughter?
My daughter is a woman.
No wonder she disappeared.
Monster, you can fool my master, but you can't fool my grandfather.
How dare you hit me?
I told you not to kill me.
Why did you do that?
Master.
Master, he's a monster.
He's gone.
Master, maybe it's true.
No, it must be Wukong.
Master.
Master, I don't think you can change your mind.
What should we do?
Master, don't read anymore.
Master, don't change your mind.
Wukong.
Master, Wukong has made a mistake.
Don't read anymore.
Master.
You've committed two murders.
Our master and disciple are dead.
You may leave.
Master.
You saved me from Mount Wuxing.
I can't forget you.
I'm sincere.
Let me follow you.
I'll listen to you.
You've succeeded again.
It's your turn now.
Wukong can't escape from me this time.
Watch me.
Wukong.
This old man must be looking for his wife and daughter.
Wukong, don't care if he's a monster.
Go away.
Come back.
Master, I lost my daughter and wife.
Did you see them?
Uncle, I saw them.
But my brother killed them.
Why did you kill my wife?
Why did you kill my daughter?
I'll kill you.
It's not me.
Why did you kill them?
Old monster, I killed them.
Good.
I'll fight with you.
Monster, I won't fight with you again.
I won't bother you this time.
Let's see what you can do.
I've got a lot of tricks. Wait and see.
Help.
Monkey, it's your bad luck.
Brother killed another one.
This is the third one.
Wukong.
Master, he's a monster.
If you don't listen to me,
I can't take you back.
You're no longer my disciple.
Master.
Brother.
Please let me explain.
I won't listen to you.
Master, please stop reciting.
You can stop.
You're not allowed to follow me.
If you follow me again,
I'll keep reciting.
Master.
A Jie, let's go.
Yes, master.
I can't go.
You can't go to Xitian without me.
Life and death are predestined.
I don't care about you.
Besides, Ba Jie and Wu Jin are protecting me.
Master.
Are you really going to drive me away?
If you don't go,
I'll recite the spell.
Okay, I'll go.
Master.
You and I have been separated today.
I didn't get any merit.
Master, please forgive me.
I'm a holy monk.
I don't need your mercy.
Brother, what should we do?
Wu Jin, you're a good man.
Protect Master.
If there's a monster holding Master,
tell them I'm his disciple.
If they hear my name,
they won't dare to hurt Master.
Okay.
Not necessarily.
Ba Jie, don't be too proud.
Maybe one day,
you'll come to the Flower Pavilion to beg me.
That's impossible.
If one day, I beg you,
you can use my ass as a ladder.
Wu Jin, let's go.
I'll take your place.
Wu Jin, I'm leaving.
Brother.
We've driven away Sun Wukong.
Let's act now and capture Tang San Zhang.
I want to eat his flesh.
Yes.
Master, we're so happy you're back.
But you look so sad every day.
Don't you like the Flower Pavilion?
I'm worried about my master.
Didn't you say he drove you here?
Why are you so worried about him?
He's a good man.
If he hadn't saved me,
I'd still be under Wu Jin's control.
I can't believe they're going to West Pavilion.
There's still a long way to go.
I shouldn't be here.
Master, why are you still awake?
I'm wondering if Wu Kong has crossed the mountain.
I knew it.
Master, you must be thinking about him.
No, I'm not.
Wu Jin, go to sleep.
Master!
Where are you?
Hurry!
Master!
Why did he disappear?
Where are you?
Master!
Where are we going to find him?
We can ask the landlady.
Yes, let's find the landlady.
Landlady!
Come out!
Stop it!
I'm here.
What do you want?
Master, I want to ask you something.
My master went missing last night.
Where did he go?
Stop it.
I'll tell you.
Your master was taken away by someone else.
In fact, they were all bats.
Bats?
What should we do?
Master, my master was taken away.
We're going to save him.
Tell me, where is Flying Man Valley?
I'll tell you.
There's a cliff 300 miles from here.
That's Flying Man Valley.
Flying Man Valley?
I'm going to save him now.
Master, thank you.
You're not a man who eats.
Who are you?
Give it to me.
Wait for me.
Why is there no one here?
Where is your master?
Master is here.
Master, we're here to save you.
We're here to save you.
I'm not your master.
I'm your grandmother.
I knew you'd come.
Do you think I'm afraid of you?
Don't let him escape.
Wujing.
Go and find Big Brother.
Big Brother.
Wujing.
Go.
The fat pig has run away.
Forget it.
We're going to eat Tang San Zang's meat.
That's right.
Bring him out.
Master.
Wujing.
I'm going to eat you up today.
That's right.
Wujing.
Master.
You have to use steamed, roasted, fried and fried monk meat.
That's delicious.
I like them all.
Baby, let's have a monk's meal.
Wujing.
Master.
What's going on?
I caught a monster.
Monster?
Yes.
Beat him.
Wujing.
Help.
Stop fighting.
Wujing.
That's Bajie.
Bajie.
Wujing.
You can't protect Master to the West.
Why did you come here?
Wujing.
You kicked my ass.
Your ass is too fat.
I'm not interested.
Wujing.
Just say what you want.
Master misses you.
Let me ask you to go back.
Wujing.
Master has sent Bajie to catch me.
He can't let me go back.
Wujing.
After you left, Master misses you every day.
He cares about you.
So he asked me to come back and take you back.
No need.
I don't care about the flowers or the land.
I don't want to be a monk.
Master.
You really don't want to go back?
No.
Sun Wukong.
Stop.
You're a heartless monkey.
You...
I'll go first.
You don't want to be a monk.
You want to be a monster here.
You...
You!
Will you fight?
Go back.
Protect Master.
Wujing.
I can't protect Wujing anymore.
What's wrong with Wujing?
Poor Master.
He's been taken away by the monster.
Maybe he's been eaten by them now.
Didn't I tell you?
If there's a monster to catch Master,
you can say that I'm Master's disciple.
Why don't you say it?
I've said it.
They don't care.
They don't care?
Not only don't care,
they even say that you're a monkey.
What kind of monkey are you?
They even say that they'll pull your skin,
cut your throat,
stew your brain,
and cut you into pieces.
I'll kill them right away.
Senior.
Wait for me.
He ran away.
Dear,
we'll be able to eat Tang Sanzang's baby meat right away.
That's right.
We'll be able to eat it forever.
To you.
Cheers.
Master.
Senior,
why aren't you here yet?
Senior.
The monkey is back.
What should we do?
Master, let's go!
Where are you going?
Take this!
What are you doing?
Get up!
Go away!
Come on!
I'll show you what I'm made of!
Go after them!
Brother!
Are you all right?
I...
I'm leaving.
Brother!
Are you really leaving?
I'm going back to Huaguo Mountain.
Brother, I know I've let you down.
Please don't leave.
Ba-Jing!
Brother, we can't go to the West Sky without you.
Brother, please don't leave.
Ba-Jing!
Wukong!
I've wronged you in the past.
If you still hate me,
I'll apologize to you.
Master!
For 15 years,
Tang Sanzang has traveled more than 30,000 miles westward.
The four disciples have not been afraid of the evil demon.
They continue to head westward.